Rohit Chaudhari

Dhule • +918421994085 • chaudharirohit1599@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/chaudharirohit1599

Fullstack Software Developer

As a proficient Fullstack Software Developer, I specialize in crafting responsive single-page web applications using modern frameworks like Angular 14+, Spring, and Hibernate. Impressed by my problem analytical and problem-solving skills, I got promoted to "Jr. Software Developer" in 3 months while working at BosLeo Pvt Ltd and was also awarded the title of "Star Performer" at Revature.

SKILLS

Frontend Techonologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, BootStrap, Typescript, Angular 14+, RxJs, NgRx, Chrome Developer Tools, Design Principles, JSON, REST, Git, Responsive Web Design

Backend Technologies: C++, Java, OOPs, JDBC, Spring Boot, Spring Data JPA, Spring MVC, Data Structures, Algorithms, MySQL, Hibernate

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jr. Software Developer (Angular) • Full-time

06/2023 - 10/2023

BosLeo Private Limited

Maharashtra

- · Implemented features related to pet medication history tracking and inventory management
- Promoted as Jr. Software Developer within 3 Months.

Full Stack Developer - Trainee • Full-time

04/2022 - 12/2022

Revature India

Chennai

- Developed the Full stack web application and the CLI social media app.
- Awarded with the title of "Star Performer" multiple times.

Machine Learning Expert - Intern • Internship

01/2022 - 07/2022

Mass Technologies - Intern

Maharashtra

• Created a Hybrid ML model with 95% accuracy prediction.

Web Developer and SEO Expert. - Intern • Internship

06/2019 - 06/2019

Maharashtra

- Learned responsive website development, site hosting, and SEO.
- Recognized as one of the best-performing trainees during the program.
- Awarded with the book "The Power of Your Subconscious Mind" as one of the top 5 candidates.

CERTIFICATIONS

Infotech Incorporate

Full Stack Software Developer

04/2022 - 12/2022

Revature India

EDUCATION

Dr. Babasaheb Ambedkar Technological University

B. Tech. Computer Engineering. (GPA: 8.82)Dhule • 04/2018 - 12/2022

Shri. Z. B. Patil Junior College

H.S.C (Marks: 66.90%) Dhule • 03/2017 - 04/2018

Chavara English Medium School

S.S.C (Marks: 72.60%) Dhule • 03/2015 - 04/2016

PROJECTS

Food swipe (Full Stack Project)

07/2022 - 12/2022

Revature India

Role:

- Project lead, Designed the front end and created the REST API for the app.
- Designed and implemented database design for the app.

Skille

- HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Angular 14+, ngrx, rxjs, Angular material, Redux.
- Java, Spring MVC, Spring Data JPA, Hibernate, REST, MySQL

Meeter (Foundational Project)

01/2022 - 04/2022

Revature India

Role:

- Implemented business logic for the CLI app.
- Designed and implemented the database.

Skills:

• Java, JDBC, MVC, MySQL.

ML methodology for diagnosing CKD (Academic Project)

01/2022 - 07/2022

Mass Technologies

Role:

- Developed a hybrid machine learning model with 95% prediction accuracy.
- Worked as Lead developer, project flow management, and presentation.

Skills:

• Python, Pandas, NumPy, MatPlotLib, SKlearn.